<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Naoya Yamaguchi</title>
    <link>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Naoya Yamaguchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Naoya Yamaguchi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography Naoya Yamaguchi was born in Japan in 1996. He received his B.S. from Department of Mechano Informatics in The University of Tokyo in 2018. Now, he is a master course student at JSK Robotics Laboratory supervised by Prof. Masayuki Inaba and Prof. Kei Okada in The University of Tokyo. His research interests are robot hand, motion strategy and robot manipulation. He develops an original robot hand on which a lot of proximity sensors are mounted all around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awards</title>
      <link>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/awards/</guid>
      <description>Final Round of Sausu-Olympic (算数オリンピック), 2007. A-Rank score at Japan Junior Mathematical Olympiad (ジュニア数学オリンピック), 2011.  I got top 5% score (A-Rank) and participated in the Final Round. I won the Outstanding Performance Award at Kansai region(地区優秀賞).  Final Round of Kagaku-no-Koshien (科学の甲子園), 2012.  Japan High School Science Championships  A-Rank score at Japan Mathematical Olympiad (数学オリンピック), 2013.  I got top 5% score (A-Rank) and participated in the Final Round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work experiences</title>
      <link>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/experience/</guid>
      <description>America Global Training Program in Utah, America, 2010.  Attended an American school during my homestay.  Test Monitor of National Center Test for University Admissions (センター試験), 2015. Opening member of Z会東大個別指導教室プレアデス, 2015. Internship at Furukawa Electric Co., Ltd. , 2016.  Three weeks.  Information Science and Technology Education Program in Hyderabad and Bangalore, India, 2018.  Workshop with students in Indian Institute of Technology Hyderabad. Company visits at Infosys and Tata Consultancy Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://708yamaguchi.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>